<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mental HIIT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_how_to_use">How To Use</string>
    <string name="title_activity_smart_trainer">Smart Trainer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_smart_timer">Smart Timer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_manual_timer">Manual Timer</string>

    <string name="highIntensity">Focus: </string>
    <string name="lowIntensity">Rest: </string>
    <string name="reps">Reps: </string>
    <string name="cool">Cool: </string>
    <string name="time">Time: </string>
    <string name="max">Max: </string>

    <string name="dummyTimeValue">00:00</string>


    <string name="about_text">
        \tThis application was developed by Nathan Pepin\n\n\t

        This application takes knowledge about meditation and integrates it with exercise science.\n\n\t
        The hypothesis is that the progressive overload model will increase the ability to stay in the present moment when the initial stimulus is increased over time.\n\n\t
        For instance, someone who is getting started with weight lifting will generally select a lower weight that they can handle, and over time they will increase the load as they get stronger.\n\n\t
        When the increase in load is kept manageable over a long period of time, there is potential for significant increase in strength. The app applies this concept to mental focus.
        \n\n\t

        For more details, including an explanation of how to use the app, please visit:
        \n\t\t
        nathanpepin.com
        \n\n\t

        Version 2.0 is planned in the future with many new features and tools, including guided meditations to help people get started.
        \n\n\t

        The current release of the software will not contain ads, but ads are likely to be added in the release to support development.
        I want to ensure that the application is working on a wide spectrum of devices before any sort of monetization occurs, and it is difficult for me to test that as a single developer.
        \n\n\t

        I would prefer a donation based model for the app, but Google policies on apps that take donations is a little unclear.
        Many app developers report not having any issues but others report that their account got shut down.
        I am doing more research to ensure whatever I do is compliant with TOS.
        \n\n\t

        If there are any questions, comments, or suggestions please contact me through my website.
        \n\n

        Disclaimer: This app does not promise any health benefits and the app does not provide medical advice. For medical advice, please consult a qualified professional.
    </string>
</resources>
